filmingcops.com 2018-05-30

# Privacy Policy - Filming Cops

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which www.FilmingCops.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (“Users”; each, a “User”) of the [www.FilmingCops.com](http://www.generateprivacypolicy.com/account/policies/edit/www.FilmingCops.com) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services it offers.

**Anonymous Users**

Users may visit our Site anonymously.

**The Only Time We Collect Personal Information**

We do not collect information from Users unless they voluntarily submit it to us. Users do not have to supply their information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities, such as email alerts. **Cookies**  
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. Users’ web browsers place cookies on their hard drives for record-keeping purposes. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert when cookies are being sent. If Users do this, some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**Sharing Your Personal Information**  
We do not sell, trade, or share User’s personal identification information to others.

**Third Party Websites**  
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that links to the sites and services of third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
www.FilmingCops.com may update this privacy policy in the future. If we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page.  You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#cdbeb8bdbda2bfb98daba4a1a0a4a3aaaea2bdbee3aea2a0).

This document was last updated on December 28, 2013
